Finding Aid for Angela Morgan Papers 1861-1957
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Manuscripts of Books
  - Crucify Me, 1933, 2 folders (Box 40)
  - Gold on Your Pillow, 1936, 2 folders (Box 40)
  - Drum Beats Out of Heaven, 1941, 2 folders (Box 40)
  - Let Loose the Splendor, 1951 (Box 40)
  - This Rapturous World, 4 folders (Box 40)
  - Rockets to the Sun, 12 folders (Box 40)
  - Awful Rainbow, 4 linear feet
    (manuscripts and related material)
    - Awful Rainbow (Box 41)
    - Awful Rainbow (Box 42)
      (continued)
    - Awful Rainbow (Box 43)
    - Awful Rainbow (Box 44)
- Topical Files
  The Topical Files series documents Morgan's activities in several literary and publishing organizations and her public lectures and recitals.
  - Record of Transactions with the International Feature Service 1921-1923 (Box 45)
  - Lists of Books in Angela Morgan's Library, 2 folders (Box 45)
  - Papers concerning the Poetry Crusade 1937-1938, 4 folders (Box 45)
  - Mailing Lists, 7 folders (Box 45)
  - Recital Notes undated (Box 45)
  - Lyceum Club Recital 1925 (Box 45)
  - Radio Address 1931 (Box 45)
  - Philadelphia Recital 1931 (Box 45)
  - Recital Notes 1931 (Box 45)
  - Richmond Address 1933 (Box 45)
  - Recital Notes 1934-1936 (Box 45)
  - Ogontz School Recital 1935 (Box 45)
  - Recital Notes 1937-1939 (Box 45)
  - Holyoke Address 1938 (Box 45)
  - Boston Address 1938 (Box 45)
  - Tyrone Address 1939 (Box 45)
  - Short stories, articles, and essays (Box 60)
  - Wheatsworth Company 1927-1931 (Box 60)
- Miscellaneous Papers
  The Miscellaneous Papers series includes an assortment of correspondence, articles, reports and other material written or assembled by Morgan on a wide range of topics in which she had an interest.
  - 1893-1910, 20 folders (Box 45)
  - 1910-1915, 41 folders (Box 46)
  - 1916-1921, 46 folders (Box 47)
  - 1922-1934, 48 folders (Box 48)
  - 1935-1956, 31 folders (Box 49)
  - Address Books (Box 49)
  - Announcements and advertisements (Box 60)
  - Clippings (Box 60)
  - Financial (Box 60)
  - Notebooks, 2 folders (Box 60)
  - Mother's Ideas (Box 60)
  - Poignant Personal Struggle (Box 60)
  - Various titles (Box 60)
  - Poems, A-W, 2 folders (Box 60)
  - Printed
    - 1919-1943, 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Undated, 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Printed poems, 4 folders (Box 60)
    - Various notes (Box 61)
- Manuscripts and Drafts
  The Manuscripts and Drafts series contains mostly drafts and unfinished of literary manuscripts, and ideas for short stories, articles, titles, and essays.
  - Ideas 1912-1939, undated (Box 50)
    - Articles, 5 folders (Box 50)
    - Books (Box 50)
    - Fiction, 2 folders (Box 50)
    - General, 11 folders (Box 50)
    - Plays (Box 50)
    - Poems
      - Beauty Parlor (Box 50)
      - Immigrant poem (Box 50)
      - 1920-1921 (Box 50)
      - 1931 (Box 50)
      - 1933 (Box 50)
      - Undated and general, 3 folders (Box 50)
    - Recitals and lectures (Box 50)
    - Song (Box 50)
    - Story
      - How is Mary to marry? (Box 50)
      - Kinder than Life (Box 50)
      - Lakhurst (Box 50)
      - Mannequin (Box 50)
      - Undated and general (Box 50)
    - Theme (Box 50)
    - Titles
      - 1914-1936 with gaps (Box 50)
      - 1939 (Box 50)
      - Undated (Box 50)
  - Interpretations of poems (Box 51)
  - Lists (people, items, poems, things to do, etc.) (Box 51)
  - Memoranda, 9 folders (Box 51)
  - Notes and statements
    - 1918 (Box 51)
    - 1931 (Box 51)
    - From books (Box 51)
    - General and undated (Box 51)
    - Words (Box 51)
  - Radio talk (Box 51)
  - Recitals (Box 51)
  - Reviews of Morgan's work and tributes, 2 folders (Box 51)
    (includes newspaper clippings)
  - Sheet music with songs (Box 51)
  - Translations (Box 51)
  - Miscellaneous personal items (Box 51)
  - Writings: articles, essays, poems, and other works, completed and fragmentary 1906, 1912-1939, undated
    - Articles
      - Undated, 3 folders (Box 51)
      - 1927 (Box 51)
      - 1931 (Box 51)
      - Articles and stories 1920 (Box 51)
      - Articles and talks 1933 (Box 51)
      - Struggle of the Creative Worker (Box 51)
    - Broadcasts (Box 51)
    - Creative Worker (Box 51)
    - Flowers (Box 51)
    - Great Men Who Have Missed Love (Box 51)
    - Healing Instruction (Box 52)
    - Husband Jealous (Box 52)
    - Intelligence tests (Box 52)
    - Lessons, 6 folders (Box 52)
    - Let Loose the Thunder (Box 52)
    - Price She Paid (Box 52)
    - Purity (Box 52)
    - Rangely recital (Box 52)
    - Restless Sex (Box 52)
    - Poems
      - 1912-1918, 3 folders (Box 52)
      - 1920, 2 folders (Box 52)
      - 1924-1927, 2 folders (Box 52)
      - 1931, 8 folders (Box 52)
      - 1934 (Box 52)
      - 1937-1939 (Box 52)
      - Anti-War poem (Box 52)
      - Children's poems (Box 52)
      - Christmas poems (Box 52)
      - Comic and humorous poems, 2 folders (Box 52)
      - I speak to You (Box 52)
      - Labor poem (Box 52)
      - Open the Gates (Box 52)
      - Poet (Box 52)
      - General undated, 10 folders (Box 53)
    - Poetry talk (Box 53)
    - Stories
      - 1931, 2 folders (Box 53)
      - Undated (Box 53)
    - Various titles (Box 53)
    - Words (Box 53)
    - General writings (drafts and fragments of poems, speeches, articles, and other forms)
      - 1906 (Box 53)
      - 1913 (Box 53)
      - 1915-1916, 3 folders (Box 53)
      - 1917-1930, 16 folders (Box 53)
      - 1931-1939, 10 folders (Box 54)
      - 1951-1953 (Box 54)
      - Undated, 14 folders (Box 54)
      - Undated, 27 folders (Box 55)
      - Undated, 28 folders (Box 56)
      - Undated, 26 folders (Box 57)
      - Undated, 15 folders (Box 58)
- Photographs
  The photographs includes portraits of Morgan and her circle of friends, including Rebecca Shelley. Also also photos of women at work in a tailor shop, and in homemaking classes at the Boston Training School for Wives.
  - Angela Morgan, 5 folders (Box 58)
  - Boston Training School for Wives (Box 58)
  - Morgan family, 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Mount Berry trip (Box 58)
  - Thousand Islands (Rockport, Ontario) (Box 58)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, 8 folders (Box 58)
- Books by Angela Morgan
  The Books by Morgan, series contains copies of books written by Morgan, some with her marginal notes.
  - Awful Rainbow, 1932, 357 pages (Box 61)
  - God Prays, 1917, 2 copies; 24 pages (Box 61)
  - Gold On Your Pillow, 1936, 141 pages (unbound copy (Box 61)
  - Utterance, 1916, 106 pages, with Morgan's marginal notes (Box 61)
- Artifacts
  - Flowing Gold cut, 1933 (Box 61)
  - Small stone blessed by Abdul Balia 1926 (Box 61)
  - Angela Morgan's lock of hair (Box 61)
Partial Index to Correspondents
Adams, Fred Winslow, 1866-1945.
Undated, March 9, 1915, July 8, 1916, September 21, 1921, November 11, 1921, November 14, 1923, March 24, 1924, December 6, 1926 December 11, 1926, September 9, 1927, December 5, 1927, December 12, 1927, 1928 undated, January 26, 1928, January 22, 1929, December 12, 1929, 1930's undated, 1930, December 5, 1931, January ?, 1932, February 10, 1932, March 9, 1933, March 23, 1937, 1938 1939 undated.
Adams, Jane, 1860-1935
August 6, 1918 (sec.), December 26, 1918
Aked, Charles Frederic, 1864-1941.
January 22, 1908, December 13, 1909, March 15, 1910
American Neutral Conference Committee 1916
February 8, 1917
American Peace Society
December 4, 1915
Authors, League of America
1917 undated, May 25, 1917
Balch, Madly Greene, 1867 1961
December 21, 1916, April 29, 1918, April 10, 1957
Baldwin, Ruth Standish
January 16, 1920
Banning, Kendall
1879-1944 1919, 1920, 1921, 1928.
Barton, Bruce, 1886 1967
April 26, 1912
Beckley, Zoe -1961
1915, January 23, 1919
Bestor, Arthur Eugene, 1879-1944
June 14, 1916, June 21, 1916
Bigelow, William Frederick, 1879-1966
September 25, 1914, September 28, 1914, November 7, 1914, September 16, 1929, September 14, 1934, February 7, 1935, March 19, 1935
Booth, Evangeline Cory
1865-1950 October 27, 1926
Bragdon, Claude, 1866-1946
August 22, 1930, January 4, 1933, January 10, 1933, June 1, 1936
Branch, Anna Hempstead, -1937
1920, 1921, January 22, 1922, November 22, 1922, 1923 Undated, January 28, 1923, April 15, 1923, January 15, 1928, June 13, 1938 July 27, 1928, January 27, 1929, April 3-1, 1933, May 15, 1935, August 24, 1935
Bridgman, Hovard Allen, 1860-1929
August 5, 1913
Brovne, Anita
Extensive correspondence throughout
Bryce, James, Viscount, 1838-1922
April 4, 1908
Bureau of Legal First Aid
May 31, 1917, November 7, 1917
Burton, Ernest, 1856-1925
August 2, 1922
Cadman, Samuel Parkes, 1864-1936.
April 16, 1908, April 21, 1908
Carnegie, Dale, 1888-1955.
May 12, 1930, November 18, 1937
Carnegie, Louise Whitfield, 1857-1946.
1914-1918 Undated, December 2, 1915, November 19, 1915, 1916 undated, January 13, 1916, April 9, 1916, May 5, 1916, May 10,1916 (sec.), November 25, 1916, January 14, 1917, April 7, 1917, December 20, 1917, March 29, 1918, December 4, 1918, December 17, 1918, December 31, 1918, May 8, 1919, May 14, 1919, May 16, 1919, June 27, 1919, November 26, 1919, December 19, 1919, January 20, 1920, March 27, 1920, April 3, 1920, April 8, 1920, July 27, 1921, November 20, 1922, April 23, 1924, February I7, 1927
Carruth, Hayden, 1862-1932
May 8, 1908, December 17, 1909, March 14, 1910, July 16, 1913
Chamberlain, Samuel Selwyn, 1851-1916
September 1, 1907
Chautauquas [subject]
Information 1916, on the Chatauqua Institution
Cheyney, Ralph
March 18, 1931, January 28, 1933, August 11, 1933, March 20, 1937, August 10, 1937
Church Peace Union
1915, 1916, 1917, 1918, September 19, 1919
Civil War
Letter from A.T. Morgan to his mother October 20, 1861
Clark, Thomas Curtis, 1877 1954
1934, 1935
Coleman, George William, 1867-1950
February 5, 1915, September 25, 1914, October 13, 1914, October 23, 1914, March 1, 1915, December 17, 1915, December 27, 1916, 1917, undated, December 26, 1917, December 24, 1918, 1920's undated.
Conant, Isabel Fiske
January 16, 1937
Condon, Randall Judson, 1862-1931.
1925
Cooke, Edmund Vance, 1866-1932
September 29, 1917, October 7, 1919, December 11, 1929
Costain Thomas Bertram, 1885-1965.
February 12, 1929
Crow, Martha Foote,-1924)
Undated, undated 1914-1918, June 1916, December 7, 1916, December 31, 1918, 1919 undated, April 16, 1923, July 5, 1923
Debs, Theodore
September 20, 1921
Debs Memorial Radio Fund
February 10, 1928
Del Mar, Eugene, 1864-1941
January 17, 1921, November 22, 1921, March 11, 1922
Dreiser, Theodore, 1871-1945
September 12, 1910
Dutton, Samuel Train, 1849-1919
April 11, 1916, April 22, 1916, December 27, 1917, May 7, 1918
Eastman, Crystal, 1881-1928
March 3, 1917, September 28, 1917, November 28, 1917, August 15, 1918
Eastman, John Coates, 1862-1925
December 29, 1909, January 18, 1910, February 18, 1910, December 6, 1916, January 30, 1918
Eaton, Lily W.
October 31, 1915, [November 1915?], November 15, 1915, November I7, 1915, November 27, 1915, December 8, 1915, December 14, 1915, January 10, 1916, October 21, 1920, November 7, 1920, April 17, 1922, April 25, 1922, December 16, 1929
Elson, William Harris, 1856-1935
1920, August 15, 1928, October 10, 1928
Emergency Peace Campaign
December 21, 1936, January ?, 1939
Emergency Peace Federation
March 14, 1917
Erskine, John, 1879-1951
January 2, 1916, 1920 undated
Fagnani, Charles Prosperso 1854-1940
December 23, 1916, November 5, 1917, March 4, 1920
Fellowship of Reconciliation
November 6, 1915, November 8, 1915, December 27, 1915, November 2, 1916, March 24, 1917, May 22, 1917, May 29, 1917, September 11, 1917
First Church for Animal Rights
December 12, 1921
Fleischer, Charles, 1871-1942
April 3, 1916, September 7, 1916, January 16, 1923
Ford Peace Ship [subject]
1915, 1916
Fosdick, Harry Emerson, 1878-
November 28, 1934, March 24, 1937, May 20, 1938, May 24, 1938, May 28, 1938
Frank, Henry, 1854-1933.
January 3, 1910
Friends of Freedom for India
November 16, 1921
General Federation of Women's Clubs
December 8, 1921, February 8, 1922, February 27, 1922, April 8, 1922, May 10, 1930, January 27, 1931, 1932 undated, 1936, 1937 1938, 1939
Griggs, Edward Howard, -1951)
February 23, 1917
Guthrie, Kenneth Sylvan, 1871-1940
May 20, 1920, April 7, 1923, November 24, 1923, August 22, 1926
Haggard, Sewell, 1879-1928.
1915, 1916, 1917, 1918
Hammond, Emily Vanderbilt Sloane
Undated, 1914-1918 undated, 1914, 1915, 1916, 1917, 1918, 1919, 1920's undated, 1920, October 24, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1926, 1927, 1928, 1929, 1930's undated, 1930, 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1937, 1938, 1939, February 16, 1940, 1952, January 27, 1953, July 10, 1953
Hammond, John Henry, 1871-1949.
December 19, 1915, April 27, 1931
Harriman, Karl Edwin, 1875-1935.
1923, 1924, July 11, 1925, March 31, 1926
Harrison, Henry
September 20, 1930, January 8, 1931, September 17, 1934, September 27, 1934, October 8. 1934, January 9. 1936, April 26, 1937
Hays, Will Harrison, 1879-1954.
April 27, 1923, June 5, 1923, June 30, 1923, March 30, 1925
Hearst, William Randolph, 1863-1951.
December 15, 1914
Hodgkin, Henry Theodore, 1877-1933
November 6. 1915, November 8, 1915
Holmes, Burton, 1870-1958.
March 5, 1937
Holmes, John Haynes, 1879-1964.
April 11, 1914, September 23, 1914, December 7. 1915, December 19, 1917, March 29, 1918, November 12, 1918, December 24, 1918, January 13, 1919, July 28, 1919, January 12, 1920, February 3, 1920, March 17, 1920, June 28, 1920, October 20, 1920, October 25, 1920, October 27, 1920, December 2, 1920, July 19, 1921, August 15, 1921 September 27, 1921, November 10, 1921, December 27, 1921, December 29, 1921, April 21, 1922, May 2, 1922, December 7, 1922, January 5, 1923, March 8, 1923, April 18, 1923, April 27, 1923, June 19, 1923 December 12, 1923, May 21, 1924, September 30, 1924, March 27, 1925, 1926 undated, March 9, 1926, March 31, 1926, April 22, 1926, April 26, 1926, May 10, 1926, May 17, 1926, May 20, 1926, May 26, 1926, June 7, 1926, June 25, 1926, October 7, 1926, October 11, 1926, November 1, 1926, November 3, 1926, December 10, 1926, February 10, 1927, April 7, 1927, November 14, 1927, November 18, 1927, January 5, 1928, February 9, 1928, February 24, 1928, May 5, 1928, June 19, 1928, October 23, 1928, October 31, 1928, November 19, 1928, January 9, 1929, January 14, 1929, March 26, 1929, August 28, 1929, September 6, 1929, October 3, 1929, December 11, 1929, April 28, 1930, May 1, 1930, May 20, 1930, June 18, 1930, July 23, 1930, December 10, 1930, December 4, 1931, January 18, 1932, January 26, 1932, June 8, 1932, December 14, 1932, November 12, 1934, March 5, 1935, March 7, 1935, September 18, 1935, September 19, 1935, April 17, 1936, December 29, 1936, March 1, 1937, January 3, 1938, May 15, 1939, January 22, 1940, January 25, 1940, September 29, 1953, October 23, 1953, February 17, 1954
Holt, Hamilton, 1872-1951
January 9, 1917
Hoover, Herbert Clark, 1874-1964
October 7, 1952
Huebsch, B.W. 1876-1954
December 4, 1916, December 21, 1917
Industrial Workers of the World
May 11, 1926
James, William, 1842-1910
February 21, 1909
Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1853-1937
1918, 1919
Jones, Edith Lloyd
Undated, January 4, 1920, March 22, 1922, July 11, 1922, May 15, 1923
Jones, Jenkin Lloyd, 1843-1918
December 19, 1917, February 5, 1918
Keyes, Frances Parkinson
1920's undated, December 5, 1921, December 21, 1921, 1922 undated January 29, 1922, April 14, 1922, May 2, 1922, October 14, 1927
Ladd, Kate Macy, 1863 1945
Undated, 1914 19181, undated, 1915, December 16, 1916, January 8, 1917, March 7, 1917, December 17, 1918, September 26, 1919, December 31, 1919, 1920's undated, 1920, 1921, 1922, August 27, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1926, 1927, 1928, November 27, 1929, 1930, January 5, 1931, 1932, March 28, 1933, April 26, 1933, January 10, 1934, May 20, 1935
Ladd, Walter Graeme
January 7, 1916, June 24, 1916, June 30, 1916, January 5, 1917, January 11, 1918, July 1, 1918, June 2, 1919, June 11, 1919, March 12, 1920, April 10, 1920, June 10, 1920, October 14, 1920, October 21, 1920, June 15, 1921, June 28, 1921, June 16, 1922, August 2, 1922, November 14, 1922, January 5, 1923, May 21, 1923, December 12, 1923, May 12, 1924, June 11, 1924, June 30, 1924, January 25, 1926, February 19, 1926, March 27, 1926, September 10, 1928, August 9, 1930, October 15, 1930, May 18, 1931, December 16, 1932
Laidler, Harry W.
April 15, 1953
Lane, Margaret
December 21, 1916, January 8, 1917, February 9, 1917, April 10, 1917, December 14, 1917, June 8, 1918
League for the Larger Life
January 17, 1921, November 22, 1921
League of American Pen Women
March 29, 1915, April 6, 1920, April 30, 1920, November 19, 1921, January 20, 1922, March 18, 1922, March 27, 1922, April 3, 1922, December 6, 1922, March 24, 1923, April 3, 1923, May 7, 1926, December 15, 1926, October 17, 1927, January 22, 1928, January 26, 1928, February 4, 1928, 1929, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935, November 12, 1939
League of Small and Subject Nationalities
December 14, 1918
Lengel, William Charles, -1965
1921, 1922
Libby, Frederick Joseph, 1874
1936 undated, 1937 undated
Lynch, Frederick Henry, 1867 1934.
1915, December 16, 1916, August 8, 1920, January 15, 1923
McAdoo, Eleanor W.
August 20, 1918, September 9, 1918, September 20, 1918
MacManus, Seumas, 1869-1960
October 30, 1920
Markham, Anna Catherine
Undated, May 1, 1920
Markham, Edwin, 1852-1940
February 1916, December 1916, November 1926
Matthews, Brander, 1852-1929
November 2, 1922
Mooney, Tom
1931 Undated, August 5, 1931, April 23, 1935, February 3, 1936, November 9, 1937
Morgan, Albert Talmon, 1841-1922
Throughout
Morgan, G. Campbell, (1863- )
September 24, 1907, December 12, 1907, December 28, 1909, undated 1910, April 1, 1915, January 20, 1917, January 26, 1918, July 28, 1926, August 7, 1926, June 3, 1931, December 9, 1932
Musser, Benjamin Francis
January 18, 1928, January 26, 1928, February 5, 1928, May 11, 1928, April 8, 1929
National Cathedral Association
1924, 1925, December 29, 1926
National Kindergarten Association
July 15, 1915, December 14, 1916, February 26, 1917, April 4, 1917, May 10, 1917, June 14, 1917, August 16, 1917, September 13, 1917, November 12, 1917, November 26, 1917, 1918 undated, January 30, 1918, March 5, 1918, March 22, 1918
National Music League
May 18, 1927, May 25, 1927
National Unemployment League
April 16, 1930, June 13, 1930, June 27, 1930
National Woman's Party
October 17, 1928
Nearing, Scott, 1883-
December 7, 1916, July 30, 1923
O'Hara, Geoffrey, 1882-1967.
August 2, 1933, 1934, 1936, 1937, 1938
Olmsted, Mildred Scott
June 3, 1930, November 10, 1930
Paine, Albert Bigelow, 1861-1937
March 27, 1915, January 19, 1916, December 3, 1916
Paquin, Samuel Savil, 1868-1943
Correspondence throughout
Parkhurst, Charles Henry, 1842-1933.
December 24, 1909, March 11, 1910
Peale, Norman Vincent, 1898-
October 20, 1952
Pennsylvania Committee for Total Disarmament
January 28, 1932, February 23, 1932, April 6, 1932
The People's Chorus of New York
January 22, 1927, October 3, 1927, October 31, 1927, March 4, 1936
People's Council of America
June 27, 1917, August 10, 1917
People's Mandate to Governments to End War
August 14, 1939
Phelps, William Lyan, 1865-1943.
January 13, 1919, November 22, 1927, November 30, 1927, September
18, 1929
Pierpont, John [subject], 1785-1866.
September 30, 1907
Pillsbury, Parker, 1809-1898.
August 4, 1884
Poetry Society of America
Undated, February 16, 1915, April 10, 1915, January 9, 1917, December 6, 1917, December 4, 1918, December 31, 1918, 1919 undated, November 14, 1919, March 2, 1920, May 1, 1920, October 18, 1920, January 25, 1928, June 11, 1935, January 19, 1937, March 19, 1937
Randall, John Herman, 1871 1946
December 4, 1916, December 7, 1916, December 18, 1916, 1917, 1918, 1919, 1920, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1924, November 30, 1925, March 9, 1926, April 19, 1926, May 17, 1926, December 21, 1926, February 5, 1927, February 17, 1927, April 5, 1927, October 15, 1927, October 27, 1927, December 1, 1927, 1929 undated, September 3, 1929, October 8, 1929, May 2, 1930, December 11, 1930, March 20, 1931, December 30, 1931, December 20, 1932, June 3, 1938
The Rebel Poets
January 18, 1928, May 18, 1928, December 15, 1928, December 5, 1929, 1930 undated
Reynolds, Paul Revere, 1864 1944.
April 24, 1912, May 2, 1912, May 4, 1912, May 21, 1912, May 25, 1912, November 8, 1912, December 11, 1912, December 13, 1912
Rider, Fremont, 1885 1962
March 9, 1909
Robinson, Corinne Roosevelt, 1861 1933
October 31, 1915, December 21, 1915, December 11, 1916, April 4, 1918, December 29, 1919, May 13, 1920, November 26, 1921, December 13, 1929, January 31, 1932
Russell, Charles Edward, 1860-1941
July 1, 1909, April 2, 1912, November 12, 1914
Sarett, Lew, 1888-1954
April 19, 1923
Shaw, Mark Revell, 1889-
December 20, 1937
Shelley, Rebecca, 1887
September 25, 1915, September 26, 1915, October 1, 1915, October 2, 1915, October 20, 1915, October 22, 1915, October 26, 1915, October 28, 1915, November 3, 1915, November 14, 1915, November 20, 1915, November 26, 1915, November 30, 1915, December 18, 1915, July 15, 1916, August 27, 1916, September 10, 1916, September 12, 1916, December 2, 1916, December 13, 1916, December 23, 1916, December 28, 1916, December 30, 1916, December 17, 1927, March 29, 1937 November 18, 1939
Shelly, William Alfred, 1854-1930
January 1, 1916, January 27, 1916
Sinclair, Upton, 1878-1968
October 23, 1914
Smith, George Jay, 1866-
March 20, 1922, April 5, 1922, April 8, 1922, March 13, 1923, October 2, 1923
Socialist Party [subject]
November 1918
Stevenson, Burton Egbert, 1872-1962.
January 13, 1924
Stidger, William Leroy, 1885-1949.
1938
Stoner, Winifred Sackville, -1931
March 24, 1923, August 1, 1927, August 14, 1927
Tarbell, Ida Minerva, 1857-1944.
April 25, 1912
Thomas, Lowell, 1892-
November 12, 1934
Thomas, Norman Mattoon, 1884-1968.
May 29, 1917, September 11, 1917
Towne, Charles Hanson, 1877-1949.
Correspondence throughout
Trent, Lucia
Undated, January 4, 1923, February 17, 1923, 1927, 1928, 1929, 1930's undated, 1930, 1931, September 7, 1932, December 18, 1932, 1933, 1934, December 30, 1935, April 4, 1936, October 16, 1936, December 4, 1936, 1937, 1938, September 22, 1939, January 22, 1940, March 23, 1941
United Peace Chest
April 6, 1937, October 6, 1938, February 6, 1939
Van Dyke, Henry, 1852-1933.
1915 undated, June 19, 1915
The Vigilantes
April 11, 1917, 1918 undated, January 17, 1918, January 22, 1918
Villard, Fanny Garrison, 1884-1928.
March 1, 1915, April 29, 1918
Vivisection Investigation League, Inc.
September 20, 1923, June 9, 1924
Wald, Lillian D., 1867 1940.
February 1, 1923
Weatherly, Arthur
February 11, 1913, January 16, 1913, September 17, 1913, April 20, 1913, April 20, 1915, April 25, 1916, July 29, 1917, January 19, 1918, April 29, 1919, November 19, 1921, December 13, 1922, January 20, 1923, March 24, 1924, February 16, 1925, December 8, 1926, May 26, 1929, 1937, August 9, 1938
Weller, Charles Frederick, 1870-1957.
November 19, 1934, July 24, 1935
Weatherill, Samuel Price
1928, 1929, 1930, March 15, 1935, June 19, 1939, October 3, 1939
Wheeler, Edward Jewitt, 1859-1922.
March 31, 1910, June 8, 1910, July 8, 1910, February 1, 1911, April 21, 1911, November 14, 1911, November 22, 1911, March 6, 1912, December 18, 1913, October 29, 1914
White, Trumbull, 1868 1941.
May 28, 1908, December 10, 1914
Wilcox, Ella Wheeler, 1855 1919
1915 undated, April 1, 1915, October 27, 1915, October 29, 1915, December 24, 1915, January 4, 1917, June 8, 1917, October 30, 1917
Wiley, Franklin Baldwin, 1861 1930